XRP over one cycle: up 5x, then down 80%.
Most FXRP yield vaults ride that whole rollercoaster.
RotorVault doesn't: same ballpark return, half the drawdown.
-44% instead of -78%, enforced on-chain by Flare's oracle.
Deposit FXRP once. An agent proposes how to split it
across the live Firelight and Upshift vaults for yield.
But every allocation must clear an on-chain FTSOv2 gate.
This is the real Coston2 deployment: 5 FXRP, gate risk-off, held idle.
Here's what "enforced on-chain" actually means.
The agent proposed rebalance(4000, 4000) - 40% Firelight, 40% Upshift.
But the gate was risk-off, so the contract overrode it to zero.
Rebalanced(0, 0, false) - the veto is in the transaction, not a promise.
The Upshift APY comes on-chain via an FDC Web2Json attestation,
verified against Flare's FDC and bound to one source URL.
And it isn't just stored - rebalance() reads it on-chain.
A zero or stale APY forces that venue idle. FDC gates real capital.
None of this is mocked.
Our adapters are fork-tested against the real Firelight & Upshift vaults.
28 contract tests, green against live state, zero API keys.
The strategy isn't a story - it's a keyless, reproducible backtest.
Run it with zero API keys and get the same -44% drawdown.
Three Flare protocols, all doing real on-chain work:
FTSO vetoes, FAssets flows, FDC gates. RotorVault.